Dr. Julius Janušonis Contact address: Vilnius Phone: +370 63817746

Email: j.j.janusonis@gmail.com

Languages
English – C2
Russian – C2
Dutch – A2
Lithuanian – native speaker

About me

I am a physicist with a Ph.D. in material science from University of Groningen. My core competencies include experimental optical technologies, laser metrology, ultrafast spectroscopy, light interaction with matter and thin films. 8 years of optical lab experience, 5 years experience in creating optical setups, 6 years of software development experience, experience in managing R&D projects and project teams.

Work experience

2023 - CEO of LLC "Everoptics"

2017 – 2022 – Software project development and measurement device development;

2012 – 2017 – Experimental work in ultrafast spectroscopy and optical measuring device development;

2003 – 2011 – Laser-based technology development in solar cell research and development; software development, 2008 and on – team lead role; junior manager of 2 framework projects;

Education

2017 - PhD in Material science from University of Groningen

2004 – Master in Theoretical physics